<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Playadda247</string>
    <string name="loginHere">Already a member? <b>Login Here</b></string>
    <string name="signUpHere">Don\'t have an account? <b>Sign Up</b></string>
    <string name="forgotPassword">Forgot Password? <b>Reset Now</b></string>
    <string name="passwordresetmessage">Password reset link is sent to your registered email address. Please check and click on the link to reset your password.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="joining_match_no_join">You don\'t have enough Play Coins. Kindly purchase some Play Coins inorder to join this match.</string>
    <string name="joining_match_join">You have enough Play Coins to join this match.</string>

    <string name="join_dialog_txt1">\u25CF Make sure you have set your PubG Username(IGN) and not Character ID.</string>
    <string name="join_dialog_txt2">\u25CF Above PubG Username should match the username in Edit Profile Section.</string>
    <string name="join_dialog_txt3">\u25CF You can update your Pubg Username in Edit Profile Section</string>
    <string name="join_dialog_txt4">\u25CF No new PubG Account is allowed. PubG Accounts with Level > 40 are allowed.</string>
    <string name="join_dialog_acknowledgement">By participating, you accept the Fair Play Policy.</string>
    <string name="dialog_join_done">You have successfully joined the match. Room ID and Password will be shared to you 15 minutes before the match start time.</string>
    <string name="about_match_1"><b>\u25CF</b> No new PUBG accounts are allowed. PUBG accounts with level less than 40 are not allowed to participate.
        Such participants will be kicked out from the room and they will not be given refund.</string>
    <string name="about_match_2"><b>\u25CF</b> If in anyway, you fail to join the room by the match start time then we are not responsible
    for it. In such cases, Refund will not be processed. So make sur to join on time.</string>
    <string name="about_match_3"><b>\u25CF</b> Do not share the Room ID &amp; Password with anyone who has not joined the match.
    If you are found doing so, your account may get terminated and all the winnings will be lost.</string>
    <string name="about_match_4"><b>\u25CF</b> Griefing &amp; Teaming is against the game rules. Any participants found doing so,
    will be disqualified and their orizes will be lost.</string>
    <string name="about_match_5"><b>\u25CF</b> Room ID &amp; Password will be shared in the app before 15 minutes of Match Start Time.</string>
    <string name="about_match_6"><b>\u25CF</b> Match will start after 15 minutes of sharing Room ID &amp; Password</string>
    <string name="about_match_7"><b>\u25CF</b> Make sure to grab Room ID &amp; Password before the Match Start Time</string>
    <string name="about_match_8"><b>\u25CF</b> Make sure you join the Match Room ASAP, before the match starts.</string>
    <string name="about_match_9"><b>\u25CF</b> This match is a Paid Match. To participate, you have to pay the entry fee.
    There are total 100 spots available. Join it before all the spots are filled.</string>
    <string name="about_match_10"><b>\u25CF</b> Please note that the listed entry fee is per individual and not the squad/duo team</string>
    <string name="about_match_11"><b>\u25CF</b> Each member of a team (Squad or Duo) has to pay the entry fee and register individually for
    the match or tournament.</string>
    <string name="about_match_12"><b>\u25CF</b> Once you join the match custom room, do not keep changing your position. If you do so,
    you may get kicked out from the Room.</string>
    <string name="about_match_13"><b>\u25CF</b> Spots are given on the basis of First Come First Get.</string>
    <string name="about_match_14"><b>\u25CF</b> Last standing man gets the Chicken Dinner Award.</string>
    <string name="about_match_15"><b>\u25CF</b> You will be also rewarded for each kill. Check the rewards details above.</string>
    <string name="about_match_16"><b>\u25CF</b> Use only Mobile Devices to join Match. Do not use any Hacks or Emulators.</string>
    <string name="about_match_17"><b>\u25CF</b> If anyone found violating these rules then immediate action will be taken
    and respective accounts may get banned and rewards may be abandoned.</string>
    <string name="about_match_18"><b>\u25CF</b> If you have any queries then contact us on contact@shubham.com</string>
    <string name="about_match_19"><b>\u25CF</b> Also, if you want to arrange Giveaway or Sponser any such match then drop us a mail
    at contact@shubham.com</string>
    <string name="lbl_set_profile_photo">Set profile image</string>
    <string name="toast_image_intent_null">Image picker option is missing!</string>
    <string name="lbl_take_camera_picture">Take a picture</string>
    <string name="lbl_choose_from_gallery">Choose from gallery</string>
    <string name="dialog_permission_message">This app needs permission to use this feature. You can grant them in app settings.</string>
    <string name="dialog_permission_title">Grant Permissions</string>
    <string name="go_to_settings">GOTO SETTINGS</string>

    <string name="referral_msg">Share your referral code and invite your friends to earn 10 PlayCoins when they join first match. Your friends will also get 5 PlayCoins as Signup Bonus.</string>
    <string name="invite">Invite your friends to sign up</string>
    <string name="invite2">Your friends register and get rewarded</string>
    <string name="invite3">Join a match and you get rewarded</string>
    <string name="term"><u><b>Terms of Service</b></u></string>
    <string name="share_message">Addicted to PUBG! Want to make some csh out of it? Try out PlayAdda247, an eSports Platform.
        Join daily PUBG matches &amp; get rewards on each kill you score. Get huge prize on getting chicken dinner. Just download the
    PlayAdda247 android app &amp; register using the Referral code given below to get Rs 5 free sign up bonus.</string>
    <string name="write_file">This app needs access to your file storage so that it can write files.</string>
    <string name="term_refer">*T&amp;C</string>
    <string name="note">Note: In order to continue using the app, you must have to update the app to the latest version.</string>
</resources>
